Guide to the Edwin H. Armstrong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Photographs, Negatives and Lantern Slides, 1886-1967
  - Marcellus Hartley Laboratory, Columbia University
    - Apparatus Used by E.H. Armstrong in Reception of Station WEAF--Special Experimental Unit Used with Regular Transmitting Unit at Bellmore, Long Island--Demonstration Made to Dr. W.R.G. Baker, 1933 February 4 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Chassis Collection, undated (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Early Wide Band Photos, 1932-1933 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - First Alpine Modulation Equipment On Test at Columbia, 1936 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Inside Cage View of First FM Transmitter, Northeast Room, Philosophy Hall, 1932-1933 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Interior Views and Apparatus, 1925, 1927, 1930 (includes negatives), (5 Folders) (Box 275, Folder 12-16)
    - Interior Views and Apparatus, 1931-1933, 1935-1936, (10 Folders) (Box 276, Folder 1-10)
    - Interior Views and Apparatus, 1936-1939, 1943, undated, (7 Folders) (Box 277, Folder 1-8)
    - Modulation Apparatus, undated (Box 277, Folder 9)
    - Original FM Modulator and Power Amplifier Built For Use at Alpine, 1936 April 29 (Box 277, Folder 10)
    - Original Regenerative Circuit Apparatus Built By E.H. Armstrong, While a Student At Columbia University, 1943 March (Box 277, Folder 11)
    - Power Amplifier and Intermediate Power Amplifier of Frequency Modulation Transmitter, undated (includes negatives) (Box 277, Folder 12)
    - Remains of War Chassis, undated (includes negatives) (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Signal Corps Job, 1943 December 1 (includes negatives) (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - “Special Equipment”--In 201 Philosophy, 1943 January 25 (includes negatives) (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - “Timing Of Waveform”--Rejector As Set Up During WWII, undated (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Individuals, undated (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - Marconi Shack--Original
    - Armstrong, E.H. In Front of the Shack, undated (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Armstrong, E.H. and Guglielmo Marconi In Front of Shack, Rocky Point, New York, undated (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Armstrong, E.H. [and possibly Marion] In Front of Shack, Babylon, New York, undated (Box 278, Folder 8)
    - Armstrong, E.H. and Unidentified In Front of the Shack, Babylon, New York, undated (Box 278, Folder 9)
    - Moving The Shack Onto a Truck For Relocation to Rocky Point, Babylon, New York, 1930 (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - Photos of the Building Before Purchase and Relocation by E.H.Armstrong to Babylon, New York, undated (includes negatives) (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - Shack In Front of RCA Building, undated (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - The Shack In Front of RCA’s Transmitting Station, Building #1, Given as a Gift From E.H. Armstrong, Rocky Point, New York, undated (Box 278, Folder 13)
  - Marconi, Guglielmo
    - Captions of Photographs Sent to E.H. Armstrong in New York, 1953 September (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - Clifden, Ireland
      - “Marconi Express” Peat Train, undated (Box 278, Folder 15)
      - Marconi With His Engineers Including C.S. Franklin, Later to be the Designer of the S.W. Beam System, Standing at Extreme Left, 1913 (Box 278, Folder 16)
      - Transatlantic Wireless Station, undated (includes correspondence) (Box 278, Folder 17)
    - D.Station at Either Aberdeen or Flambora Head, undated (Box 278, Folder 18)
    - Images From “Marconi Jubilee 1897-1947,” undated (Box 278, Folder 19)
    - Images From “Wireless at Sea” By H.E. Hancock, Monument and English Royalty Near Poldhu Station, undated (Box 278, Folder 20)
    - Images From Wireless World, by H.E. Hancock--Marconi at Signal Hill With Instruments, undated (Box 278, Folder 21)
    - Marconi’s Diary For 1901 December 12-13, In Which He Recorded In Ink the Times of His Reception of the First Transatlantic Wireless Signals, undated (Box 278, Folder 22)
    - Marconi In The Room at Signal Hill, St. Johns, Newfoundland With Apparatus Used to Receive the First Transatlantic Wireless Signals in 1901 December, undated (Box 278, Folder 23)
    - Marconi Station at Siasconset, Nantucket, Massachusetts, undated (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Poldhu, Cornwall (Box 278)
      - Exterior View In 1923, undated (negative only) (Box 278, Folder 24)
      - Poldhu Wireless Station--Used For the First Transoceanic Service For Wireless Telegraphy, undated (Box 278, Folder 25)
      - Tonkin, Charles, William Gilbert, Edward Hodge, and James Exelby, of Mullion at Fiftieth Anniversary of the First Spanning of the Atlantic by wireless, 1951 December 12 (Box 278, Folder 26)
    - Preparing the Kite Which Raised the Receiving Aerial at St. John’s, Newfoundland With Which Marconi Received the First Transatlantic Wireless Signals in 1901, undated (Box 278, Folder 27)
    - Transatlantic High Power Marconi Station at Glace Bay, Nova Scotia, undated (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Transatlantic Station at South Wellfleet, Cape Cod, Massachusetts, undated (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - Notebooks
    - Contains Military Photographs--Handwritten Note by Armstrong About his Grandfather’s Cat--News Clippings, undated (Box 278, Folder 28)
    - Contains Wedding Notice of Emily Gertrude Smith to John Armstrong--Reception Notice From the Smiths--William West McIntosh Oration Note--News Clippings, undated (Box 278, Folder 29)
    - Scrapbook Belonging to Emily Gertrude Smith--Includes Derthick Farm, Howard's School Examination, Marriage Announcement, Howard's Completion of Credits for the Degree of Electrical Engineering, John Armstrong's Obituary, Pupin Announcement of Wireless Invention, Captain Edwin H. Armstrong, and News Clippings, 1886-1901, (2 Folders) (Box 279, Folder 1-2)
  - Pupin, Michael I.
    - Armstrong, E.H. Speaking at Funeral Service, undated (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Pupin Holding the John Fritz Medal and Dr. Edwin Wilbur Rice, Jr. Holding the Edison Medal Presented by the American Institute of Electrical Engineering, 1931 January 27 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Early Laboratory Picture, undated (includes negative) (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Exterior View, Holding Papers, undated (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Postcard of Hemlock Farm, the Residence of M.I. Pupin, in Norfolk, Connecticut, undated (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Radio Club of America
    - 40th and 41st Annual Banquet, Advertising Club of N.Y., 1949, 1950 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Annual Banquets--Including Presentations of the Armstrong Medal to Harry W. Houck, J.V.L. Hogan, Charles S. Ballantine, and Henry J. Round, 1936-1939, 1941, 1947, 1949-1953 (Box 282, Folder 12)
    - Banquet--Hotel Ansonia, 1919 November 19 (Box 282, Folder 13)
    - Banquet Smoker Beefsteak Dinner, Brooklyn, New York, 1931 April 22 (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - Dinner for Captain Round, 1929 October 4 (Box 282, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript of Article From The Wireless Age accompanying Photograph of Banquet Given in Honor of Armstrong, E.H. on 1919 November 19, 1919 December (Box 279, Folder 8)
    - Members at Dinner for Captain H.J. Round, New York, 1929 October 4 (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - Reprint of Proclamation Upon the Death of E.H. Armstrong, undated (Box 279, Folder 10)
  - Radio Engineering Labs (REL)
    - Armstrong Modulator, undated (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - FM Receiver, undated (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Production Plant and Equipment, undated (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Transmitter Equipment--Open Cabinet Views, undated (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Two Way Car Equipment, undated (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - R.C.A. Communications
    - Long Wave Receivers at Riverhead, undated (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Radio Central Building Transmitters and Antennas, undated (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Short Wave Receivers and Rack, Riverhead, Long Island, undated (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Switchboard at RCAC Central Office, Broad St., New York, undated (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Transmitter Apparatus Used in Transoceanic Service, undated (Box 280, Folder 10)
  - Superheterodyne Receiver
    - Experimental Wave Heterodyne Receiver Side View, Navy Yard, New York, 1920 January 3 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - First Superheterodyne Installed At the Seagate Station by the US Navy in 1918 1941 May 19 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - First Superheterodyne Radio Receiver Developed in 1917, undated (includes correspondence) (Box 280, Folder 13)
    - Interior Of the Original Receiver Built on the Second Harmonic Principle, undated (Box 280, Folder 14)
    - Portable Unit With Which an Inexperienced Woman Heard 2LO During the Tests Run by Radio Broadcast and Wireless World, undated (includes negative) (Box 280, Folder 15)
    - Second Superheterodyne Radio Receiver Developed In 1922, undated (Box 280, Folder 16)
    - Six-Tube Receiver, undated (includes negative) (Box 280, Folder 17)
    - Third Superheterodyne Radio Receiver With Five-Tube Layout and Loudspeaker, undated (Box 280, Folder 18)
    - US National Museum Exhibit With Regenerative and Superheterodyne Receivers, 1955 (Box 280, Folder 19)
  - Washington, D.C.
    - Columbia University Professor E.H. Armstrong Explains New Radio Broadcast System to F.C.C., 1936 June 17 (Box 280, Folder 20)
      - Testifies Before the House Labor Committee, 1918 January 15 (Box 280, Folder 21)
  - Westhampton, New York
    - Armstrong Receiving Apparatus at Home of George Burghard, undated (includes negatives) (Box 280, Folder 22)
    - Notarized Photos of Equipment With Notes--Armstrong vs. Hansell Interference, 1937 September 20 (Box 280, Folder 23)
    - Receiving Apparatus, 1934 June (includes negative) (Box 280, Folder 24)
    - Receiving Apparatus, 1936 June (Box 280, Folder 25)
    - Westhampton, Pre-Hurricane, undated (includes negatives) (Box 280, Folder 26)
    - Westhampton Recorder Pictures by Fred Hargesheimer, 1947 (Box 280, Folder 27)
  - World War I
    - Armstrong, E.H. in Uniform With the Rank of Captain in the Signal Corps, undated (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Major Armstrong in Uniform, undated (includes negative) (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Signal Corps--France
      - Armstrong, E.H. and Unidentified Individual in Airplane (Armstrong Developed First Airplane Radios During WWI), undated (Box 281, Folder 3)
      - Armstrong, E.H. Receiving Legion d’Honneur, 1919 (Box 281, Folder 4)
      - Group Photographs, undated (Box 281, Folder 5)
      - Interior Views of Radio Apparatus, undated (Box 281, Folder 6)
      - Major Armstrong and Professor Abraham, undated (Box 281, Folder 7)
      - Major Armstrong, General Ferrié, and Professor Abraham of Sorbonne, [Hindenbreg] Chateau, undated (Box 281, Folder 8)
      - Tank Radio Apparatus, undated (Box 281, Folder 9)
      - US Army Official Photos of Radio Apparatus, undated (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Swiss and French Mobilization (Box 281, Folder 11)
  - Yonkers, New York
    - Armstrong, E.H. Visiting His Boyhood Bedroom Where In 1912 He Made the Discovery of Regeneration, 1947 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - Billboard For United States Tires Mentioning E.H. Armstrong, 1921 (Box 281, Folder 13)
    - Dismantling of Radio Pole at 1032 Warburton Avenue--Includes correspondence from Bradley Hammond, 1935 August (includes negatives) (Box 281, Folder 14)
    - Re-Erection of Runyon tower At The Home of Frank A Gunther In Staten Island, New York, 1967 (includes correspondence) (Box 281, Folder 15)
    - Runyon Tower--E.H. Armstrong and Unidentified Individuals, 1946 January (Box 281, Folder 16)
  - Zenith Corporation
    - FM Radio Assembly Line, undated (Box 281, Folder 17)
    - FM Station W51C Studio--Office and Transmitting Apparatus, 1943 August 16 (Box 281, Folder 18)
  - Lantern Slides
    - Alpine, NJ (duplicate)
      - Armstrong, E.H. and Charley Fowler Wearing Homemade Ice Shields, 1941 January 18 (2 slides) (Box 285, Folder 1-2)
      - Armstrong, E.H. and Harry “The Rigger” Jorgenson on Turnstile Antenna, undated (9 slides) (Box 285, Folder 3-12)
      - High Power Amplifier Shielded Behind Copper Screening, undated (Box 285, Folder 13)
      - Osborn, Perry In the Control Room, 1941 September 29 (2 slides) (Box 285, Folder 14-15)
      - Pre-Construction Site, 1937 March 29 (Box 285, Folder 16)
      - Radio Tower--Including Air View, View of Base, View from Ground, View During Construction, undated (13 slides) (Box 285, Folder 17-30)
      - W2XMN Building, undated (Box 285, Folder 31)
      - Unidentified Individual on Radio Tower, undated (Box 285, Folder 32)
    - Apparatus
      - Alpine, NJ--Including Early Model of Intermediate Stages, FM Apparatus, High Power Apparatus and Intermediate Power Stage Apparatus, undated (17 slides, duplicate) (Box 285, Folder 33-49)
      - Antenna, undated (Box 285, Folder 50)
      - Cables at Base of Pole, undated (Box 285, Folder 51)
      - Empire State Building--Transmitters Installed by E.H.Armstrong, 1934-1935 (3 slides) (duplicate) (Box 285, Folder 52-54)
      - Hartley Laboratory, undated (7 slides) (duplicate) (Box 285, Folder 55-61)
      - [Regenerative Receiver Setup], undated (Box 285, Folder 62)
      - [High Power Amplifier Stage], undated (duplicate) (Box 285, Folder 63)
      - Predistortion, undated (3 slides) (Box 285, Folder 64-66)
      - Radio Tower Antenna, undated (Box 285, Folder 67)
      - Radio Set--Frank Eisemann FM, General Electric FM (duplicate)--Pilot FM and AM, Stromberg Carlson Console Radio, Zenith, undated (6 slides) (Box 285, Folder 68-73)
      - Radio Set Including Headset and Microphone, undated (3 slides) (duplicate) (Box 285, Folder 74-76)
      - REL--Frequency Modulation, undated (15 slides) (Box 286, Folder 1-15)
      - Top of Radio Pole and Antenna, undated (Box 286, Folder 16)
      - Westhampton, NY-- Armstrong Receiving Apparatus at the Home of George Burghard, undated (3 slides) (duplicate) (Box 286, Folder 17-19)
      - Yonkers, NY-- W2AG, undated (4 slides) (duplicate) (Box 286, Folder 20-23)
      - Unidentified, undated (43 slides) (Box 286, Folder 24-66)
      - Glass Plate Negatives--4" x 5" (Box 295)
        - Unidentified, undated (2 slides) (Box 295, Folder 1-2)
    - Bull’s Eye, undated (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Cartoons--Patent Lawyers, undated (20 slides) (Box 287, Folder 2-21)
    - Color Image of Flower Vase, undated (duplicate) (Box 287, Folder 22)
    - De Forest, Lee--Patent Application for Radio Signaling Systems, 1915 September 21 (16 slides) (Box 287, Folder 23-38)
    - Early Family and Childhood--“1032” Radio Pole, Early Radio Aerial, undated (3 slides) (duplicate) (Box 287, Folder 39-41)
    - Exhibit Showing Effect of Modern Static-Reducing Antenna
      - Carnavon Signal at Riverhead, NY, 1926 April 27 (2 slides) (Box 287, Folder 42-43)
      - Recorder Tape Showing Diversity Effect, undated (2 slides) (Box 287, Folder 44-45)
    - Exterior Views [Generator Plant], undated (14 slides) (Box 287, Folder 46-59)
    - FCC-- Table of Sound-Video Reception (Which Appears Twice in 1945 Feburary 21 FCC Brief, Pages 15, 30), undated (Box 287, Folder 60)
    - Figures
      - Audion--Capacity Coupling, Circuit,Grid Current, Operating Characteristics, Wing Current, undated (8 slides) (Box 287, Folder 61-68)
      - Block Diagram--Titled “Fig 1” and “Fig 2”, undated (2 slides) (Box 287, Folder 69-70)
      - Circuit Diagram-- Titled “Fig 1” through “Fig 4”, undated (6 slides) (Box 288, Folder 1-6)
      - Colpitta Circuit As Printed in the New York Herald Daily Hookup, 1924 March 22 (Box 288, Folder 7-8)
      - Energy Polar Diagram, undated (Box 288, Folder 9)
      - “Frequency Modulation Signaling System,” E.H. Armstrong Patent--Figures 2 through 14, 1940 December 17 (24 slides) (Box 288, Folder 10-33)
      - Percentage of Listening Hours During the Last Sunspot Cycle, undated (Box 288, Folder 34)
      - Plots
        - Grid Current vs. Grid Voltage (2 slides) (Box 288, Folder 35-36)
        - Hand-Drawn Sinusoid Showing Envelope, undated (Box 288, Folder 37)
        - Hand-Drawn Block Diagram, undated (4 slides) (Box 288, Folder 38-41)
        - Hand-Drawn Circuit Diagram, undated (3 slides) (Box 288, Folder 42-44)
        - Percent Distortion R.M.S. of Correction Amplifier and Modulator (4 slides) (Box 288, Folder 45-48)
        - Signal-Noise vs. Distance, 1939 September 25 (2 slides) (Box 288, Folder 49-50)
        - Square of A.C. Component of Telephone Current, undated (4 slides) (Box 288, Folder 51-54)
      - Plaintiff’s Exhibit--Antenna System at Poldhu, Cornwall in 1923, undated (Box 288, Folder 55)
      - Plate Tuning--Receiver Unit Tuning, Unit Transmitter, Distribution of Potential, Method of Keeping In Step a Two Unit Transmitter, undated (4 slides) (Box 288, Folder 56-59)
      - Set of Lecture Slides--Experimental Setup, Cord and Tuning Fork, Circuit Diagram, Section of Cable, Plots, undated (13 slides) (Box 288, Folder 60-72)
      - Slides Used With IRE Paper “Method of Reducing the Effect of Atmospheric Disturbances”--Figures 1 through 10, Circuit Drawings, 1927 October 5 (20 slides) (Box 289, Folder 1-20)
      - Slides Used With R.C.A. Paper “A Study of the Operating Characteristics of the Radio Detector and Its Place In Radio History”--Figures 1 through 19, A through D, Advertisement Featuring Seeley, 1948 (27 slides) (Box 289, Folder 21-47)
      - Slides Used with Technical Paper “A Method of Reducing Disturbances In Radio Signaling By a System of Frequency Modulation”--Figures 1 through 7, 1935 November 6 (19 slides) (includes original and final versions of figures) (Box 289, Folder 48-66)
      - Slides Used with Technical Paper “A Method of Reducing Disturbances In Radio Signaling By a System of Frequency Modulation”--Figures 8 through 34, 1935 November 6 (43 slides) (includes original and final versions of figures) (Box 290, Folder 1-43)
      - “The Super-Heterodyne”--Armstrong Paper Presented Before the IRE--Figures 2 through 6, 1924 (7 slides) (Box 290, Folder 44-50)
      - Radio Frequency Signaling Circuit, undated (Box 290, Folder 51)
      - Relation Between EMF and Current-- +R -R, +R >-R, +R=-R, undated (3 slides) (Box 290, Folder 52-54)
      - Wave Propagation, undated (Box 290, Folder 55)
      - Wave Intensity, undated (Box 290, Folder 56)
      - Wireless Receiving System Patent 1,113,149--Inventor E.H. Armstrong--Figures 1 through 4, 1914 October 6 (6 slides) (Box 290, Folder 57-62)
      - “Some Recent Developments of Regenerative Receivers-- Armstrong Technical Paper--Figures 1 through 3,9 through 15, 1922 June 7 (12 slides) (Box 290, Folder 63-74)
    - Haddonfield, NJ-- Early Antenna for FM Reception, Receiving Antenna, 1934 June, 1934-1935 (5 slides) (duplicate) (Box 291, Folder 1-5)
    - Hartley Laboratory-- Taken By J. Boldtman In the Presence of T.J. Styles, 1927-1933 (glass plate negatives--8"x11") (7 slides) (duplicate) (Box 295, Folder 3-9)
    - Hartley Laboratory--Interior View, undated (2 slides) (duplicate) (Box 291, Folder 6-7)
    - Maps
      - FM Broadcast Station Construction Permits Issued, Stations In Operation, Applications Filed But Not Yet Acted Upon by FCC,1941 March 15 (6 slides) (Box 291, Folder 8-13)
      - Principal Radio Stations in New England and Road Map, 1940 (Box 291, Folder 14)
      - Alpine Tower Broadcasting Range, 1940 April 18 (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Marconi Cape Cod Power Station-- Conical Antenna, undated (2 slides) (duplicate) (Box 291, Folder 16-17)
    - Meeting Notes, 1935 November (2 slides) (Box 291, Folder 18-19)
    - New York Times Front Page--As Transmitted by Facsimile Over FM, As Published in Radio Today, 1936 April, 1934 November 24 (2 slides) (duplicate) (Box 291, Folder 20-21)
    - Oscilllograms--Regeneration, Station W2XMN Recorded at Andaulsia, Penna--Slides Marked 1 through 14, 1945 June 16, undated (25 slides) (Box 291, Folder 22-46)
    - Palisades--View of the River, Unidentified, undated (5 slides, duplicate) (Box 291, Folder 47-51)
    - PHILCO Radio Set Advertisement, 1941 (2 slides) (Box 291, Folder 52-53)
    - Pupin, Michael I--Lecture Slides 1 through 12, undated (12 slides) (Box 291, Folder 54-65)
    - Pupin, Michael I--Lecture Slides 13 through 42, undated (30 slides) (Box 292, Folder 1-30)
    - Radio Engineering Lab (REL)--Production Plant, undated (duplicate) (Box 292, Folder 31)
    - RCA (duplicate)
      - Antennas at Radio Central, Apparatus, undated (5 slides) (Box 292, Folder 32-36)
      - Alexandarson Alternator, undated (2 slides) (Box 292, Folder 37-38)
      - Long Wave Towers and Receivers at Riverhead, undated (4 slides) (Box 292, Folder 39-42)
      - Radio Central Building, undated (4 slides) (Box 292, Folder 43-46)
      - Shortwave Receivers and Rack, Riverhead, Long Island, undated (2 slides) (Box 292, Folder 47-48)
      - Switchboard at Central Office, Showing Foreign Stations, New York City, undated (4 slides) (Box 292, Folder 49-52)
      - Transmitter Apparatus Used in Transoceanic Service, undated (6 slides) (Box 292, Folder 53-58)
    - Radio Aerial--Including Unidentified House, undated (7 slides, duplicate) (Box 292, Folder 59-65)
    - Radio Tower, undated (4 slides) (Box 293, Folder 1-4)
    - San Bruno Point Wireless Station (9 slides) (Box 293, Folder 5-13)
    - Schloemich and Von Bronk Patent--First Page, undated (2 slides) (Box 293, Folder 14-15)
    - Solar Flares, undated (2 slides) (Box 293, Folder 16-17)
    - Superheterodyne (duplicate)
      - Chassis, Four-Tube Layout With Loudspeaker, Original Receiver, Six-Tube Receiver, Interior View, Unidentified Man with Apparatus, undated (12 slides) (Box 293, Folder 18-29)
      - First Version, Dismantled Receiver, Six-Tube Receiver with Speaker, undated (glass lantern slides, 8"x11", 6 slides) (Box 295, Folder 10-15)
    - Tables-- London Television Voice Channel--Maximum and Minimum Field Strengths, Deerfield Receiving Station, undated (3 slides) (Box 293, Folder 30-32)
    - Transmission Lines, undated (Box 293, Folder 33)
    - View of Landscape, undated (4 slides) (Box 293, Folder 34-37)
    - WWI--General Ferrie and Professor Abraham of the Sorbonne in France, undated (2 slides, duplicate) (Box 293, Folder 38-39)
    - X-Radiograph--Coins, Feet, Hand, Lower Leg, Torso, undated (12 slides) (Box 293, Folder 40-51)
    - Yankee Network
      - Mount Washington-- Engineer on Radio Pole, Inside of Antenna Coupling House and Coupling Equipment, Radio Pole, Building, Rime-Covered Radio Tower, undated (6 slides, duplicate) (Box 293, Folder 52-57)
      - Radio Pole--Interior View of Apparatus, undated (2 slides) (Box 293, Folder 58-60)
      - WDRC--Buildings and Radio Pole, 1939 (4 slides) (Box 293, Folder 61-64)
      - W1XOJ--Building, Car and Trailer, undated (6 slides) (Box 293, Folder 65-70)
      - W1XOJ-- Radio Pole, undated (3 slides) (Box 294, Folder 1-3)
      - W2XMN Building, Base of Alpine Radio Tower, undated (2 slides, duplicate) (Box 294, Folder 4-5)
      - W2XRA
        - Radio Plots, 1945 July 28 (Box 294, Folder 6)
        - Comparison of FM Service Areas Available on 46 and 105 MC, undated (Box 294, Folder 7)
        - Monthly Tabulation Sheet, 1945 August (2 slides) (Box 294, Folder 8-9)
      - W45CM--Gunther and Nafzger, undated (duplicate) (Box 294, Folder 10)
      - WTMJ--Back of the Milwaukee Journal Radio Car, undated (3 slides) (Box 294, Folder 11-13)
    - Yonkers, New York--"1032 Pole", undated (2 slides) (duplicate) (Box 294, Folder 14-15)
    - Unidentified Individuals--With Apparatus, On Icy Radio Tower, Ski Slope, Radio Tower, Outside, In Shed, On Rime-Covered Radio Pole, In the Palisades, With Radio Apparatus, undated (20 slides) (Box 294, Folder 16-35)
    - Unidentified Tangle of Wires, undated (duplicate) (Box 294, Folder 36)